{
  "name": "Unit 3",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "\"beat\" o‘zbekchada nima?",
      "answers": ["yengmoq", "chalmoq", "tashlamoq", "to‘plash"],
      "correct_answer": 0,
      "time": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "\"board game\" o‘zbekchada nima?",
      "answers": ["doska o‘yini", "kompyuter o‘yini", "yugurish", "futbol"],
      "correct_answer": 0,
      "time": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "\"captain\" o‘zbekchada nima?",
      "answers": ["sardor", "o‘yinchi", "hakam", "murabbiy"],
      "correct_answer": 0,
      "time": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "\"challenge\" o‘zbekchada nima?",
      "answers": ["chaqiruv", "yordam", "yozuv", "o‘yinchoq"],
      "correct_answer": 0,
      "time": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "\"champion\" o‘zbekchada nima?",
      "answers": ["chempion", "musobaqa", "o‘yin", "qo‘shiqchi"],
      "correct_answer": 0,
      "time": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "\"cheat\" o‘zbekchada nima?",
      "answers": ["g‘irromlik qilmoq", "yugurmoq", "ichmoq", "ko‘tarilmoq"],
      "correct_answer": 0,
      "time": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "\"classical music\" o‘zbekchada nima?",
      "answers": ["mumtoz musiqa", "xalq musiqa", "zamonaviy musiqa", "konsert"],
      "correct_answer": 0,
      "time": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "\"club\" o‘zbekchada nima?",
      "answers": ["klub", "shifokor", "do‘kon", "stadion"],
      "correct_answer": 0,
      "time": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "\"coach\" o‘zbekchada nima?",
      "answers": ["murabbiy", "hakam", "sardor", "tomoshabin"],
      "correct_answer": 0,
      "time": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "\"competition\" o‘zbekchada nima?",
      "answers": ["musobaqa", "o‘yin", "konsert", "qo‘shiq"],
      "correct_answer": 0,
      "time": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "\"concert\" o‘zbekchada nima?",
      "answers": ["konsert", "musobaqa", "o‘quv", "kurs"],
      "correct_answer": 0,
      "time": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "\"defeat\" o‘zbekchada nima?",
      "answers": ["mag‘lub etmoq", "yordam bermoq", "chaqirmoq", "kuzatmoq"],
      "correct_answer": 0,
      "time": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "\"entertaining\" o‘zbekchada nima?",
      "answers": ["ko‘ngilochar", "qorong‘i", "mashhur", "qiyin"],
      "correct_answer": 0,
      "time": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "\"folk music\" o‘zbekchada nima?",
      "answers": ["folklor musiqa", "mumtoz musiqa", "jaz", "rap"],
      "correct_answer": 0,
      "time": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "\"group\" o‘zbekchada nima?",
      "answers": ["guruh", "doska", "ovoz", "sahna"],
      "correct_answer": 0,
      "time": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "\"gym\" o‘zbekchada nima?",
      "answers": ["zal", "musobaqa", "stadion", "konsert zali"],
      "correct_answer": 0,
      "time": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "\"have fun\" o‘zbekchada nima?",
      "answers": ["xursandchilik qilmoq", "o‘qimoq", "yig‘lamoq", "yutqazmoq"],
      "correct_answer": 0,
      "time": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "\"interest\" o‘zbekchada nima?",
      "answers": ["qiziqtirmoq", "yig‘moq", "suzmoq", "to‘xtamoq"],
      "correct_answer": 0,
      "time": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "\"member\" o‘zbekchada nima?",
      "answers": ["a'zo", "murabbiy", "dushman", "tomoshabin"],
      "correct_answer": 0,
      "time": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "\"opponent\" o‘zbekchada nima?",
      "answers": ["raqib", "do‘st", "sardor", "muhokama"],
      "correct_answer": 0,
      "time": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "\"organize\" o‘zbekchada nima?",
      "answers": ["tashkillashtirmoq", "yig‘lamoq", "qo‘shiq aytmoq", "suzmoq"],
      "correct_answer": 0,
      "time": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "\"pleasure\" o‘zbekchada nima?",
      "answers": ["rohat", "azob", "shovqin", "sovuq"],
      "correct_answer": 0,
      "time": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "\"referee\" o‘zbekchada nima?",
      "answers": ["hakam", "murabbiy", "sardor", "o‘yinchi"],
      "correct_answer": 0,
      "time": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "\"rhythm\" o‘zbekchada nima?",
      "answers": ["marom", "qo‘shiq", "tezlik", "harakat"],
      "correct_answer": 0,
      "time": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "\"risk\" o‘zbekchada nima?",
      "answers": ["tavakkal qilmoq", "qochmoq", "yig‘lamoq", "aytmoq"],
      "correct_answer": 0,
      "time": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "\"score\" o‘zbekchada nima?",
      "answers": ["ochko ishlamoq", "sakramoq", "chizmoq", "tozalamoq"],
      "correct_answer": 0,
      "time": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "\"support\" o‘zbekchada nima?",
      "answers": ["qo‘llab-quvvatlamoq", "to‘xtatmoq", "boshlamoq", "o‘ynamoq"],
      "correct_answer": 0,
      "time": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "\"team\" o‘zbekchada nima?",
      "answers": ["jamoa", "o‘yin", "dars", "qo‘shiq"],
      "correct_answer": 0,
      "time": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "\"train\" o‘zbekchada nima?",
      "answers": ["trenirovka qilmoq", "ketmoq", "kuzatmoq", "ovqatlanmoq"],
      "correct_answer": 0,
      "time": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "\"video game\" o‘zbekchada nima?",
      "answers": ["video o‘yin", "musobaqa", "konsert", "do‘kon o‘yini"],
      "correct_answer": 0,
      "time": 10
    },

    ### UNIT 6

    {
      "question": "\"achieve\" o‘zbekchada nima?",
      "answers": ["erishmoq", "yig‘lamoq", "o‘qimoq", "aytmoq"],
      "correct_answer": 0,
      "time": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "\"brain\" o‘zbekchada nima?",
      "answers": ["miya", "bo‘y", "qo‘l", "oyoq"],
      "correct_answer": 0,
      "time": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "\"clever\" o‘zbekchada nima?",
      "answers": ["aqlli", "yoqimsiz", "zerikarli", "shovqinli"],
      "correct_answer": 0,
      "time": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "\"concentrate\" o‘zbekchada nima?",
      "answers": ["diqqatni jamlamoq", "yugurmoq", "suzmoq", "chizmoq"],
      "correct_answer": 0,
      "time": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "\"consider\" o‘zbekchada nima?",
      "answers": ["o‘ylab ko‘rmoq", "qochmoq", "aylanmoq", "tushmoq"],
      "correct_answer": 0,
      "time": 10
    }
  ]
}
